Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Division of Paleobotany Archives
1838-2014
PBAR.000001
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
10
several filing cabinets, shelves
The archives of the Division of Paleobotany, including those of the Princteton University paleobotanical collections.
Division of Paleobotany, Yale Peabody Museum
Biographical Sketch
The Yale Peabody Museum?s paleobotany collection numbers over 150,000 specimens, with 4,200 of these type and illustrated specimens. The collection is worldwide in scope, with approximately 75% of the collection from North America and the other 25% from the Arctic, Australia, Central American, Europe, Israel, Pakistan, Lebanon, South America and the West Indies.
Tracing its roots back to the early 19th century, this collection is one of the most historically significant in the United States. Included among its riches are plant fossils from the opening of the American West, from the Wilkes Expedition of 1838?1842 described by James Dwight Dana, Triassic and late Cretaceous floras from New York, New Jersey and southern New England; and the world?s largest assemblage of cycadeoids.
Over the past 20 years the collection has seen unparalleled growth. Part of this expansion is the result of field collecting, but the largest increase is from the addition of 2 orphaned collections: The New York Botanical Garden Collection and a substantial part of the Princeton University paleobotanical collections. These holdings include material that formed the basis of the research of many of the founders of American paleobotany, including J.S. Newberry, Leo Lesquereux, E.W. Berry, W.M. Fontaine, Lester Ward and Arthur Hollick.
The Peabody?s paleobotany collection also has under its care the Compendium Index of North American Mesozoic and Cenozoic Type Fossil Plants.
Description of the Material
Archives of the Division of Paleobotany, including those of the Princteton University paleobotanical collections.
Connecticut; North America; Maps; Correspondence; Prints; Miscellaneous; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Maps, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Maps of the Division of Paleobotony.
  - Atlas Maps. United States., 000008
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: Montana Scale: 1: 250 000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1894; 000885
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: Wyoming Scale: 1: 125000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1896; 000884
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: District of Columbia Maryland to Virginia Scale: 1: 62500 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1901; 000878
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: Wyoming-South Dakota-Montana Scale: 1: 125 000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1905; 000880
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: Barnesboro-Patton Scale: 1:62500 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1913; 000879
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: Michigan Scale: 1: 62500 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1917; 000881
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: South Carolina and North Carolina Scale: 1: 62500 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1931; 000883
    - Geologic Atlas of the United States. Location: Pennsylvannia Scale: 1: 62500 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1945; 000882
    - Pennsylvanian Geology of the Cumberland Plateau. Location: Cumberland Plateau Scale: Publisher: State of Tennessee Department of Conservation Division of Geology, 1956; 000889
    - United States. Quadrangle: NE Virginia Scale: 1 in to 1 mile Publisher: Historic Urban Plans, 1865; 000870
    - United States. Quadrangle: Southwestern Scale: 1:2851200 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1959; 000872
    - United States. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7603200 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1961; 000871
    - United States. Quadrangle: South Central Scale: 1: 2 851 200 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1961; 000874
    - United States. Quadrangle: South General Scale: 1:2 851 200 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1966; 000873
    - United States. Quadrangle: Central Mississippi Valley States Scale: 1: 2 000 000 Publisher: US Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1967; 000875
    - United States. Quadrangle: Central Plains States Scale: 1: 2 000 000 Publisher: US Dept. of the Interior Geological Survey, 1976; 000876
    - United States. Quadrangle: Northern Plains Scale: 1: 1: 2 440 000 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1986; 000877
  - Atlas Maps. International., 000009
    - Asia Pacific. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 23000000 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1989; 000865
    - Europe. Quadrangle: British Isles Scale: 1: 837 440 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1958; 000866
    - Europe. Quadrangle: Poland and Czechoslovakia Scale: 1: 2 154 240 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1958; 000867
    - Europe. Quadrangle: Germany Scale: 1: 520640 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1959; 000869
    - Europe. Quadrangle: France, Belgium, and the Netherlands Scale: 1: 2154240 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1960; 000868
    - Geological picture of the ancient bohemia. Location: Scale: Publisher: Dr. Anton Fric, 1906; 000886
    - Paleotectonic Maps Jurassic System. Location: Scale: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1956; 000887
    - Paleotectonic Maps Triassic System. Location: Scale: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1959; 000888
    - World Atlas. Location: Scale: varies Publisher: Rand Mc Nally & Co., 1950; 000890
  - Geologic Maps. United States., 000005
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Hartford South Scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longitude: N413730-W723730 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1954-1962; 000763
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Clinton Scale: 1:24000 Latitude/Longitude: n4115-w723730 Publisher: Geological and Natural History Survet, 1954; 000764
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: New Britain Scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longitude: N413730-W7245 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1959; 000762
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Bristol Scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longitude: N413730-W7300 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1961; 000761
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: New Britain Scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longitude: N413730-W7245 Publisher: US Geological Survey Bedrock Map, 1966; 000765
    - Connecticut. Scale: 1: 500 000 Publisher: CT Geological and Natural History Survey Tectonic Map, 1985; 000766
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 125 000 Latitude/Longitude: n30-w30 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1985; 000784
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 125 000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1985; 000786
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 125 000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1985; 000787
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 125 000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1985; 000788
    - Connecticut. Quadrangle: Litchfield and New Haven Counties Scale: 1: 12 000 Latitude/Longitude: N412612-W730938 Publisher: Department of the Interior United States Geological Survey, 2006; 000785
    - Iowa. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N41-W91 Publisher: Iowa Geological Survey, 1937; 000789
    - Maryland. Quadrangle: Cecil County Scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longitude: N20-W50 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1902; 000793
    - Maryland. Quadrangle: St. Mary's County Scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longitude: N3800-W20 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1903; 000790
    - Maryland. Quadrangle: Anne Arundel County Scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longitude: N3845-W25 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1916; 000791
    - Maryland. Quadrangle: Prince Georges County and the District of Columbia Scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longitude: N35-W40 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1951; 000792
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Fort Benton Scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4700-W11100 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1899; 000767
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Little Belt Mts. Scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4600-W11100 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1899; 000768
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Fort Benton Scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4700-W11100 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1899; 000769
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 750 000 Latitude/Longitude: N45-W105 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1948; 000795
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Scale: 1:750 000 Latitude/Longitude: N45-W110 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1948; 000796
    - Montana. Quadrangle: Jefferson Basin Scale: ? Latitude/Longitude: ? Publisher: Geological Society of America, 000794
    - New York. Quadrangle: Catskill and Kaaterskill Scale: 1:65200 Latitude/Longitude: N4200-W7415 Publisher: University of the State of NY, 1928-1936; 000770
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hudson-Mohawk Scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4200-W73730 Publisher: New York State Museum and Science Survey, 1970; 000771
    - New York. Quadrangle: Lower Hudson Scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N402230-W7530 Publisher: New York State Museum and Science Service, 1970; 000798
    - New York. Quadrangle: Hudson-Mohawk Scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4200-W73730 Publisher: New York State Geological Survey, 1987; 000799
    - New York. Quadrangle: Lower Hudson Scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4015-W7530 Publisher: New York State Geological Survey, 1989; 000797
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N46-W97 Publisher: United States Department of the Interior Geoloical Survey, 1921; 000801
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N46-W97 Publisher: United States Department of the Interior Geoloical Survey, 1927; 000800
    - North Dakota. Latitude/Longitude: N46-W104 Publisher: North Dakota Geological Survey 3 copies, 1956; 000772
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: n46-w97 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1965; 000803
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Golden Valley Formation Scale: 1: 250 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4630-W10130 Publisher: U.S. Geological Survey, 1977; 000802
    - North Dakota. Latitude/Longitude: N46-W97 Publisher: North Dakota Geological Survey Bedrock Map, 1982; 000773
    - Oklahoma. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N34-W95* Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1954; 000804
    - Rhode Island. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 100 000 Publisher: Office of Rhode Island State Geologist, 1994; 000805
    - United States. Quadrangle: Pacific Southwest Region Scale: 1in=30 miles Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1966-1968; 000808
    - United States. Quadrangle: Kansas, Oklahoma, Missouri, Arkansas Scale: 1: 1 875 000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1966; 000806
    - United States. Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N25-W80 Publisher: US Geological Survey Shows tectonic features, 1967; 000775
    - United States. Quadrangle: Alaska Scale: 1; 7 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N55-W135 Publisher: US Geological Survey Tectonic Features, 1968; 000776
    - United States. Quadrangle: Northeastern Region Scale: Varies Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1976; 000807
    - United States. Scale: 1:7500000 Latitude/Longitude: N25-W75 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1986; 000774
    - United States. Quadrangle: Great Lakes Region Scale: 1in=30 miles Publisher: US Geological Survey, 000809
    - Wyoming & Montana. Quadrangle: Bighorn Basin Scale: ? Latitude/Longitude: N4400-W10800 Publisher: United States Department of the Interior Geoloical Survey, 1947; 000811
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Ishawooa Scale: 1:125 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4400-W11000 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1893-1897; 000778
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hartville Scale: 1:125000 Latitude/Longitude: N4200-W10500 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1902; 000777
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: N/A Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N41-W111 Publisher: Department of the Interior United States Geological Survey, 1955; 000810
  - Geologic Maps. International., 000006
    - Australia. Quadrangle: Victoria Scale: N/A Latitude/Longitude: N39-W141 Publisher: Geological Survey of Victoria, 1963; 000812
    - Australia. Quadrangle: Casterton Scale: 1 Mile to 1 inch Latitude/Longitude: N3745-W14100 Publisher: Geological Survey of Victoria, 1967; 000779
    - Canada. Quadrangle: Island of Newfoundland Scale: 1: 1 000 000 Latitude/Longitude: N47-W59 Publisher: Geological Survey of Canada, 1967; 000780
    - Canada. Quadrangle: Alberta Scale: 1 inch: 25 miles Publisher: Canadian Society of Petroleum Geologists, 1981; 000813
    - England and Wales. Quadrangle: West Fleet and Weymouth Scale: 1:50 000 Latitude/Longitude: N205-W5040 Publisher: Institute of Geological Sciences, 1974; 000814
    - Federal Republic of Dutchland. Quadrangle: Hannover Scale: 1: 1000 000 Latitude/Longitude: N48-W13 Publisher: German Geological Survey, 1973; 000815
    - France. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 1000 000 Latitude/Longitude: N44-W4 Publisher: Department of Trade and Commerce, 1933; 000816
    - Great Britain. Quadrangle: Hastings and Dungeness Scale: 1: 50 000 Latitude/Longitude: ? Publisher: British Geological Survey, 1863-1864; 000818
    - Great Britain. Quadrangle: Scarborough Scale: One inch to one statute mile Latitude/Longitude: N547-W016 Publisher: Institute of Geological Sciences, 1950; 000781
    - Great Britain. Quadrangle: Horsham Scale: 1:63360 Latitude/Longitude: N510-W025 Publisher: Ordinance Survey of Great Britain, 1972; 000783
    - Great Britain. Quadrangle: Swanage Scale: 1: 50 000 Latitude/Longitude: N5030-W215 Publisher: Ordinance Survey of Great Britain, 1976; 000782
    - Great Britain. Quadrangle: Isle of Wight Scale: 1:50 000 Latitude/Longitude: N5035-W135 Publisher: Ordinance Survey of Great Britain, 1976; 000817
    - New Brunswick. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 500 000 Latitude/Longitude: N4500-W6900 Publisher: Department of Natural Resources, 1968; 000819
    - Northern South America-Amazon. Quadrangle: Scale: N/A Latitude/Longitude: N18-W32 Publisher: Geological Society of America, 1492; 000820
    - Nova Scotia. Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 640 000 Publisher: Atlantic Geoscience Society, 1989; 000821
    - Ontario. Quadrangle: East Central Sheet Scale: 1: 013760 Latitude/Longitude: N4600-W7700 Publisher: Ontario Dept. of Mines and Northern Affairs, 1971; 000822
    - Ontario. Quadrangle: Southern Sheet Scale: 1: 013760 Latitude/Longitude: N4200-W7500 Publisher: Ontario Dept. of Mines and Northern Affairs, 1971; 000823
    - South America. Quadrangle: Scale: 1:5000000 Latitude/Longitude: N50-W20* Publisher: Geological Society of America, 1950; 000824
    - United Kingdom North. Quadrangle: N/A Scale: 1: 625 000 Latitude/Longitude: N5430-W2 Publisher: Institute of Geological Sciences, 1979; 000825
    - United Kingdom South. Quadrangle: N/A Scale: 1:625 000 Latitude/Longitude: N50-W130 Publisher: Institute of Geological Sciences, 1979; 000826
  - Highway Maps. United States., 000007
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Coordinates: N4600-W9700 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1960; 000832
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dunn County Coordinates: N4730-W10220 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1960; 000840
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dunn County Coordinates: N4710-W10220 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1960; 000842
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Adams County Coordinates: N4600-W10200 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000827
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Billings County Coordinates: N4640-W10320 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000828
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mc Kenzie County Coordinates: N4750-W10330 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000829
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Billings County Coordinates: N4640-W10320 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000830
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Slope County Coordinates: N4620-W10300 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000831
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Golden Valley County Coordinates: N4640-W10340 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000833
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Morton County Coordinates: N4640-W10130 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000835
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer County Coordinates: N4700-W10150 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000836
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mercer County Coordinates: N4720-W10130 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000837
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Billings County Coordinates: N4640-W10320 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000838
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Stark County Coordinates: N4640-W10240 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1962; 000841
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Stark County Coordinates: N4640-W10210 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1965; 000834
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Dunn County Coordinates: Publisher:, 000839
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Converse County Coordinates: N4300-W10530 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1954; 000852
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Converse County Coordinates: N4300-W10500 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1954; 000853
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Fremont County Coordinates: N4250-W10740 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1955; 000843
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Fremont County Coordinates: N4310-W10810 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1955; 000844
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Fremont County Coordinates: N4250-W10840 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1955; 000850
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Fremont County Coordinates: N4220-W10810 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1955; 000851
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Campbell County Coordinates: N4330-W10510 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000854
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Campbell County Coordinates: N4350-W10510 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000857
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Campbell County Coordinates: N4440-W10510 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000858
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Campbell County Coordinates: N4420-W10510 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000859
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Johnson County Coordinates: N4330-W10610 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000860
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Johnson County Coordinates: N4410-W10640 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000861
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Johnson County Coordinates: N4330-W10640 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000862
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Johnson County Coordinates: N4410-W10610 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1956; 000863
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hot Springs County Coordinates: N4340-W10830 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1960; 000864
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheridan County Coordinates: N4440-W10650 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000845
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Park County Coordinates: N4440-W10840 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000846
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Park County Coordinates: N4420-W10840 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000847
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Park County Coordinates: N4440-W10920 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000848
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Park County Coordinates: N4420-W10920 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000849
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheridan County Coordinates: N4440-W10610 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000855
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Park County Coordinates: N4350-W10920 Publisher: US Dept. of Commerce Bureau of Public Roads, 1961; 000856
  - Miscellaneous Maps., 000010
    - Alaska. Map Type: Vegetation Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 7 500 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1966; 000892
    - Alaska. Map Type: Land Surface Form Quadrangle: Scale: 1:7 500 000 and 1: 7 000 000 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1969; 000891
    - California. Map Type: Land Map Quadrangle: Scale: 1 in to 12 miles Coordinates: Publisher: US Dept. of the Interior General Land Office, 1944; 000893
    - California. Map Type: Land Map US Quadrangle: Southern Scale: Coordinates: N33-W115 Publisher:, 1944; 000894
    - Countries of the Caribbean. Map Type: Cartographic Section Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 6 000 000 Coordinates: N3-W63 Publisher: The National Geographic Magazine, 1947; 000895
    - Glacial Lake Missoula and Channeled Scabland. Map Type: Quadrangle: Scale: Coordinates: Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1992; 000896
    - Global Navigation and Planning Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: GNC 20 1: 5 000 000 Defense Mapping Agency Aerospace Center, 1958; 000942
    - Global Navigation and Planning Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: GNC 8N 1: 5 000 000 Defense Mapping Agency Aerospace Center, 1965; 000941
    - Jet Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: JNC-86 1: 2 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1970; 000945
    - Jet Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: JNC 45 1:2 000 000 Defense Mapping Agency Aerospace Center, 1971; 000946
    - Jet Navigation Chart. Map Type: Aeronautical Specifics: JNC-100N 1:2 000 000 Aeronautical Information Section, HQ Support Command, RAAF, Victoria Barracks, Melbourne, 1971; 000948
    - Map of the US Natl Parks, Monuments, Forest, Indian Reservations, Wildlife Refuges, Public Lands, and Historical Boudaries. Map Type: Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 3 168 000 Coordinates: NN23-W74 Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1964; 000897
    - Montana-North Dakota. Map Type: Index Map Quadrangle: Scale: 1: 100 000 Coordinates: N4730-10400 Publisher: Montana Bureau of Mines and Geology, 1989; 000911
    - Montana. Map Type: Quadrangle: Ruby River from Ramshorn Creek Scale: 1:31680 Coordinates: Publisher: US Geological Survey, 1934; 000908
    - Montana. Map Type: Forest Map Quadrangle: Principle Meridian Scale: Coordinates: N4430-W20 Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1947; 000902
    - Montana. Map Type: Forest Map Quadrangle: Beaverhead National Park (east half) Scale: Coordinates: N4430-W20 Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1947; 000905
    - Montana. Map Type: Agriculture Quadrangle: Beaverhead National Forest Lima Ranger District Scale: Coordinates: N-W11230 Publisher: US Deparment of Agriculture and Forest Service, 1963; 000898
    - Montana. Map Type: Agriculture Quadrangle: Beaverhead National Forest Dillion Ranger District North Half Scale: Coordinates: N-W11230 Publisher:, 1963; 000899
    - Montana. Map Type: Agriculture Quadrangle: Beartooth Primitive Area-Cruster National Forest Scale: .5 in to 1 mile Coordinates: Publisher: US Deparment of Agriculture and Forest Service, 1968; 000910
    - Montana. Map Type: Forest Map Quadrangle: Beaverhead National Forest (East Half) Scale: .5 in to 1 mile Coordinates: N4430-W20 Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1970; 000901
    - Montana. Map Type: Forest Map Quadrangle: Gallatin Natl Forest East Scale: .5 in to 1 mile Coordinates: N4500-W40 Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1970; 000903
    - Montana. Map Type: Forest Map Quadrangle: Gallatin Natl Forest West Scale: .5 in to 1 mile Coordinates: N4430-W11030 Publisher: US Dept. of Agriculture United States Forest Service, 1970; 000904